Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/aimanmarzuqi-mokhtar-7ab13a49 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Budgets Hospitality Hotels

Aiman Marzuqi Mokhtar

Information Technology Manager at Sheraton Hotels & Resorts Kuala Lumpur

Summary

Experienced Information Technology Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospitality industry. Skilled in Budgeting, MICROS, Hospitality Management, Payroll, and Hotel Management. Strong information technology professional with a Higher national diploma focused in Business information Technology from Mara Professional College.

Experience

Sheraton Hotels & Resorts Information Technology Manager June 2019 - Present (2 years 7 months) Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia

New World Petaling Jaya Hotel IT Manager September 2018 - May 2019 (9 months) Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Sheraton Petaling Jaya IT Manager May 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 4 months) Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia

Sheraton Imperial Kuala Lumpur Hotel 1 year 5 months

IT Manager March 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 2 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Assistant Manager IT December 2015 - February 2016 (3 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia Qliq Damansara Information Technology October 2015 - November 2015 (2 months)

Novotel Kuala Lumpur City Centre IT August 2014 - September 2015 (1 year 2 months)

Sheraton Imperial Kuala Lumpur Hotel 3 years 5 months

Assistant Manager IT
December 2012 - October 2013 (11 months)

IT Executive
June 2010 - December 2012 (2 years 7 months)

The Westin Langkawi Resort
IT officer
May 2008 - June 2010 (2 years 2 months)

Huacomm Telecommunication IT Support January 2008 - May 2008 (5 months) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Broadband Support focused on Hotel Guest
- Monitoring network structure

Education

Mara Professional College

Higher national diploma, Business information Technology · (2004 - 2007)